Wow! Here it comes! That's amazing! It's so cute! Easy to ride!
And I bought it!
Kamita
I'm buying a car! Yay!
Hello everyone!
I'm Suka Tomita from Hyugaizaka46!
I've been looking at old cars and SUVs in the first, second, and third levels.
I've been looking at SUVs and other vehicles that I like.
I did a lot of research, and I found something that I like. I had a fateful encounter
I had a fateful encounter that I found.
Today, I finally decided on the car I want to buy!
I wanted to drive it one last time to make a decision.
I'm going to ask you to come to my place now.
I'll be waiting for you!
Isn't the weather beautiful?
Too nice for a drive!
Actually, it was supposed to be cloudy today.
But it's been clear and sunny since this morning!
Ta-da!
You've got it! I knew I had it in me!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Do you think he'll come?
Is he coming? Is it coming?
Is it coming soon?
What do you think I bought?
I'm buying it. I'm buying it now. I'm buying, and I'm buying now.
Oh! What? What? Is it coming already?
Aah! What? Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
It's coming! It's coming!
Haaaaahhhhh!
Cute!
What's that, it's so cute! Oh no!
Here it comes!
Wow! Hello!
Oh, my gosh! He's so cute!
Oh!
I'm so happy!
Rock, paper, scissors!
I can't look directly at it.
So, the car I'm buying today is
Mr. Suzuki's Jimny Sierra!
Yay! Look!
Full chez!
It's a color called Jungle Green to match this car today.
I also came in green!
If you've seen my reaction to this car, you'll know what I mean...
I fell in love with it!
I'm in love.
I really fell in love with this car at first sight. I really fell in love with this car at first sight.
I looked at a lot of cars, but
I knew this was the first one
I thought it was the best car for me to drive.
I decided on this car.
I had a hard time deciding, but there were many colors to choose from.
Ivory, jungle green, gray, blue, etc.
There were a lot of colors.
I really liked this color, so I decided on jungle green.
I decided on jungle green.
How do you like it?
It's a jungle, isn't it?
Good morning.
My name is Suzuka Tomita.
I look forward to working with you today.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you very much.
Wow! I missed you!
My Jimmy Sierra.
Lovely.
Really beautiful!
I wonder if they're going to make the tires bigger or something...
I don't know, but this color is still cute.
Lastly, it's not my car yet.
No, it's not.
Yes, it's the store owner's car. Yes, it's the shoppers' car.
May I take a look at it as I turn it around?
Yes, please, go ahead.
This one here in black is cute, isn't it?
This one's a little different. It's cute.
Is this original?
Yes, it's the original.
And the blinker mirrors. The mirrors here.
It's a blinker.
Stylish.
It's got this, too.
Visor's on here, too.
Tires are here.
They're Dunlop tires.
It's the highest grade.
Oh, I see.
It's got 15-inch factory aluminum.
They're nice.
It's a little blue-ish.
They match the color of the car.
Yes, they match.
So, the back of the car is, you know...
It's nice here.
This one, too.
Rear tire
This rugged look is my type. This rugged feeling is my type after all.
That's where the push button comes in, isn't it?
Here you go!
Wow, it looks like it can hold a lot!
Wow, I can go anywhere with this.
I've got one car.
Excuse me.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, wow.
It's pretty spacious.
It's nice. It looks like it could be a regular ride.
Maybe we can take a break from work.
I'm going to work in this car.
I'd like to drive it somewhere... someday.
It's so cute.
Wow.
Wow, it smells new.
It's registered and used, and I don't have the right to drive it, so I haven't used it in any way.
Thank you so much for getting it in that condition.
It's not my car yet.
Ta-da!
Wow!
Cute!
This place is cute, too.
I see a lot of people changing this part.
I see it. I'll take a look.
I'm going to change this place a little bit to my feeling someday, aren't I?
When I feel like myself.
I love it here too!
I think the best part of the car is this grille.
I personally like the grille, but there are some types of grills that I like.
It's nice and rugged.
Excuse me.
Oh!
Wow!
Jean!
Huh.
It's kind of spacious, isn't it? I knew it!
This is, you know, something that can be converted from 2-wheel drive to 4-wheel drive, right?
Yes, sir.
The Jimmy Sierra has 4-wheel drive.
Yes, this is the switch.
Right now, it's in the normal 2-quin position.
And the front edge is 4-quin, so...
Oh, the engine is button-operated
Yes, it's a push button start.
And the ETC is on this side.
Wow, wow, it's got navigation.
Wow. Thank you.
Cute. What do you think, guys?
I think I'm gonna sleep well today. I think I'm gonna sleep better today.
May I take a test ride?
Yes, I'd like to take a ride.
Yes, please.
Excuse me.
Wow.
Oh, no!
I drove it in the first car, right? It's totally different. If I sign the contract, it'll be my own car.
I can't help but get attached to it. I feel like I can love it even with its flaws.
Well, so far it doesn't have a single flaw, but I'm going to start driving it now.
I'd like to drive... for the first time... to show you driving on film. Shall we go?
Shall we go? Are we going? Shall I start the engine?
The engine's pretty quiet. I'll turn on the air conditioning.
I'll check the mirrors and adjust the side mirrors.
Okay, side brake is down.
Here we go.
Oh!
Oh! Surprisingly easy to ride!
Wow! It's easier than I thought it would be!
Okay, let's turn around a bit.
I'd like to go from the asphalt to the gravel road.
Wow, here we go, gravel.
Oh!
It's shaking.
How's it going?How's it going?
Are you good? Driving.
How is it?
Better than I expected.
Better than expected?
I knew it. I guess it's all coming out.
You're so serious.
I'm serious.
Let's go one more round.
Wow, that's good! It's totally fine!
I thought it might be more difficult to ride because of the rocking.
I thought it might be a little difficult to ride, but it's so expensive.
Wow, not at all.
It's totally great.
Oh, I see.
Wow, it's nice. And the side mirrors are big and easy to see.
I'm going to stop, right? Ah, it's small and easy to turn around, I knew it.
There's nothing but a parking lot.
Yes, it looks like this.
It's very comfortable to drive.
It's totally safe.
May I have some money for gas?
How was it compared to how you imagined?
It's much easier to drive than I imagined.
The sides are compact, so it's easy to drive.
I had a gut feeling that it would suit me. I had a normal intuition that it was a good fit for me.
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy with the view!
It's like it's my car now!
It's great, great, great!
So...
I test drove a Jiminy Sierra here today, and today I...
I'm buying a car!
Wow!
The lot is too big!
I'd like to buy this Jiminy Sierra.
Can I buy it?
Thank you very much.
I'm in... I signed a contract with my mouth...
I've already said my piece.
I'll pay for it... and I've been saving up for it.
I've already put down all the money for the purchase.
Thank you very much.
Please reply with your name, date of birth, first name, model number, etc. if you don't mind.
I tremble when I write my name.
Is it expensive?
Yes, I've never made such an expensive purchase before. Yes, I've never made such an expensive purchase!
Thank you very much.
I'm so nervous. I'll press the button.
Okay.
Oh! I got it!
This concludes the contract. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Please wait a little while until the car is delivered.
Thank you very much. I'm looking forward to it. I bought it!
I'm so happy!
Now that the deal is done, I'm going to enjoy my car life.
If you liked this video, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to my channel.
Suzuka, what about car insurance? I have Sony Sonpo!